The path to the Fairy King has been
spoken of only among the royal family
of Marinforest for generations.
It is a light of hope
that one loved by the king
left for their descendants.
Beyond here is where I'll find Tiara.
Elliot, you wait here.
I can't do that.
I am Your Highness's attendant.
I cannot allow my master to go alone.
All right.
Prince Aquasteed is always
so calm and collected,
but not when it comes to his beloved
Lady Tiararose, it seems.
I must be there to support him.
I will save Tiara, whatever it takes.
Right. Let's go!
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Hold Me... Tighter
This is a rather impressive path.
The type I imagine
the Forest Fairy King would like.
Yes. Keith, the Fairy King,
is most likely up ahead.
I just have no way of knowing how far.
It is a magic path, after all.
I've been trying to search
and inspect the surrounding area,
but it isn't working.
I see.
If you can't do it,
it would be difficult for anyone.
If something happens to Tiara
while we're stuck here...
Prince Aquasteed!
Thorns? What in the world is this?
It's a trap set by the Forest Fairy King.
A trap? But why?
He must really not want us
to go any further.
Tiara...
I'll be taking her.
Prince Aquasteed, please
don't press too far forward.
We don't know what traps might
lie ahead. It's dangerous.
No matter how dangerous
it may be, I'm still going.
I have to get to Tiara
as quickly as possible.
Prince Aquasteed!
Move aside, sky!
Let's hurry, Elliot.
R-Right.
I can't tell who is
whose attendant anymore.
Tiara...
Oh, Tiara's awake!
Tiara!
Have some fruit with us!
They're so cute.
But... why are there fairies here?
Oh, that's right.
Keith brought me here against my will.
I need to get back quickly.
K-Keith?
The king isn't here right now.
Play with us, Tiara!
What? I don't mind playing, but I want
to go back to the castle for now.
Eat this! Eat this!
All right, I will.
It's delicious!
Eat this, too!
It's a strawberry!
We have apples, too!
Well, I can't turn down
the fairies' goodwill.
Eat lots!
This is too much!
I can't eat this much!
Thank you. I'm full now.
Oh, good!
Was it yummy?
Yes, very. All the blessings
of the forest are so delicious.
It's as if the forest is enveloping me.
It feels so comfortable
and calming, but...
Fairies, I'd like
to go home to the castle.
How can I do that?
You're leaving already?
We want to play!
I'm sorry. I'll play with you next time.
This way.
This way, this way!
Come this way!
That way?
What? A kitchen?
But why...
The king had it prepared just for you.
What? Keith did?
It did seem like he enjoyed
the sweets I made, but...
These are sweet.
And these are salty.
And these are very spicy!
So they're flowers and nuts
to use as seasonings?
May I taste them?
You may!
That's sweet!
The pink flowers are sugar,
and the blue ones are salt.
The red flowers are spicy,
and I bet I could use
the yellow ones as pepper.
These make a tasty soup
when you stew them!
The fairies of the forest are amazing!
Tiara, make some sweets!
Make sweets!
What? Right now?
B-But seeing Prince Aqua
is my first priority right now.
Please!
We'll help!
And when the sweets are done,
we'll show you the way!
We'll help! We'll help!
I guess you're not going to let me
go home until I make some sweets.
This feels so strange.
The ingredients aren't what I usually use,
so I'm kind of looking forward to
seeing how they taste.
We'll put in the flowers!
Flutter, flutter!
Huh? That's the sweet flower
I tasted before.
It's not as sweet as sugar,
and it looks nice, so I guess it's fine.
I wish I had these seasonings.
But...
How would it look if I told the guy
who kidnapped me that I wanted seasonings?
I'll finish up with some flowers
for garnish, and...
The cupcakes are done!
Yummy!
Cupcakes are yummy!
I'm so glad. Now, be sure
to take me to the exit, okay?
You can count on us!
We'll take you there, Tiara!
Here it is!
Open it! Open it!
I'm finally at the exit!
This is...
not an exit.
Just what is this place?
Is that a throne?
It seems so lonely somehow.
I need to get back now.
Prince Aqua might be worried about me.
He saw me with Keith.
If I saw Keith with
another girl, I'd be jealous.
I don't want any more
misunderstandings between us.
Who's Prince Aqua?
He's my fiancé.
Is that the person you love?
Yes. I love him very much.
Prince Aqua has made
his love for me very clear.
And yet...
The compelling force of an
otome game is a terrifying thing.
I really don't understand humans at all.
Huh?!
K-Keith?!
U-Um...
Please stop this! Why must you...
Do you want to go back to the castle?
Of course I do!
Why?
I don't want to trouble
Prince Aqua any further!
I don't want to be a burden to him!
Just the fact that she's loved
by the forest fairies means
not only is she not a burden, but she's
contributing plenty to the kingdom.
Humans really are such a hassle.
You need only wait, princess.
He's here.
Tiara!
Prince Aqua?!
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Let go of Tiara, Fairy King Keith.
And if I refuse?
I will take her back by force
if I must, of course.
A human king and a fairy king
mustn't fight over me!
Please stop!
Even if you are a fairy king,
I will not allow you
to lay hands on Tiara!
Hah. Don't you already have all
the women you could ever want?
The only one I need is Tiara!
Don't make me laugh.
Tiara has felt uneasy all this time.
And it was you
who made her feel that way.
No matter who you are...
fairy king or not...
I won't let you have Tiara!
Keith, please stop this!
Tiara, you shouldn't interfere
in a battle between men.
Isn't that right?
Do you really believe a mere human
can defeat a fairy king?
Even if the odds are against me,
I cannot afford to lose!
For a human, you aren't half bad.
A king must be strong!
He needs to hold up his kingdom
and protect what's important!
Hmm... Indeed, the kings of the past
excelled in the martial arts, as well.
You stopped my blade with a fan?!
Now it's my turn.
Here I come.
Wh-Where is this?
A cliff?
I see now. We're on top of a mountain.
Yes, the tallest one.
I can look down upon everything
in this kingdom from here.
The kingdom?
It sounds as if he's
protecting the kingdom.
If you fall, you're dead.
So as long as I don't fall, I'm fine.
Water!
Ah, he can make his magic
surround his sword?
Interesting.
At this distance, Tiara shouldn't
be close enough to get hurt.
Wind!
I don't want Prince Aqua
or Keith to get hurt.
Maybe I'm being selfish,
but I want them both to stay safe.
Was that shallow?
Water!
Prince Aqua! Keith! Please stop this!
Tiara!
Wind!
P-Prince Aqua?
At last...
At last, I get to hold you.
Prince Aqua...
I know I've made you feel uneasy,
all because I lack strength.
I'm sorry.
No... No, that's not true.
You've made time for me every single day.
I'm the one who's in the wrong
for being jealous of Lady Icilla.
You were jealous? Over me?
A-At a time like this?
I'm sorry.
I know it's imprudent of me, but knowing
you felt that way makes me happy.
Prince Aqua...
Tiara, hold on tight!
I-I will!
Oddly, even in the situation
we're in, I don't feel scared.
I know that Prince Aqua will keep me safe.
Fairies of the sky,
hear my voice and answer!
Really, he's always so reckless.
Facing off against a fairy king?
He's left me with no choice.
I owe you a debt, sky fairies.
Sky, become my wings and catch me!
How beautiful...
Prince Aqua is trying his hardest
to protect this beautiful kingdom.
How wonderful. I want to
support this kingdom with him.
Tiara?
Oh, nothing. I feel as if I was
worrying over something truly trivial.
But from now on...
I think I'll be able to
work even more by your side.
Now, please don't ever do
anything like this again!
Understand?
One Hour of Lecturing
We're sorry.
I'm sorry, Tiara.
We'll spend even more time
together from now on.
I suppose I'll just have to
visit you more frequently.
I feel like that's not quite right.
Tiara is busy spending her time with me.
Unfortunately, I fear she will have
little time for official business
such as audiences with fairy kings.
You've gotten a lot more cheeky
in such a short time.
I'll just come visit her at night, then.
Then I will simply share
a bedroom with her.
Stop it right now!
A human king and fairy king working
together to help Marinforest grow...
That would be the ideal thing
for this kingdom.
Isn't there any way
to make them get along?
Tiara, have some sweets!
Let's eat together!
That's it!
Thank you!
If they eat some sweets,
maybe they'll feel happy and get along.
But there's only one cupcake.
There!
Tiara?
I made this with the fairies earlier.
I love Prince Aqua,
but I want to work with the forest fairies
to make this kingdom more prosperous.
So I split this in half.
If the two kings work together,
this kingdom can prosper even more.
That won't be enough.
Indeed.
Huh?
I told you not to touch my fiancée.
You'll support this kingdom
by my side, won't you?
Here. Eat.
Sweet.
Eat this, too.
Flowers gifted to me by both of them...
It makes them taste doubly sweet.
Yes.
That's good.
They were fighting just moments ago.
Maybe these two have more
in common than I thought?
It's like Tiara is the king!
It's true! I feel as if I have
two kings at my service now!
You really are great, Tiara.
Th-This is not a laughing matter!
I've begun to look forward to
this kingdom's future a bit.
Blessings on the Teary Bride
A wedding is the biggest
event in a girl's life!
I'll have to congratulate them a bunch!
I won't let anyone get in my way!